Guide to the Randolph Linsly Simpson African-American Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Series I. Visual Material
  - POSTCARDS
    - E.N.S. "'Befo the Wah' An Ante Bellum Story," Stamped recto beneath image of old man seated in chair, white scarf, bedroll on his back, hat in lap, two very young children stand beside. Postcard, circa 1920 (Box 25)
      Advertising card for bath and massage parlor of Dr. Colt Merriam.
      Item #1129
    - Frank E. Cooper, New York, NY "70W 'Lift Every Voice and Sing' by Augusta Savage"; view of sculpture at 1939 World's Fair. Postcard in color (Box 25)
      Item #1130
    - Acmegraph Co., Chicago, IL "6264 The Old Slave Block in the Old St. Louis Hotel, New Orleans, La. The colored woman standing on the block was sold for $1500.00..." recto beneath image. Postcard in light color, circa 1914 (Box 25)
      Item #1131
    - Unknown printer "-All hands on deck-Farewell to Gloeck. Thursday Eve. Dec. 13th. '34:" man prepares to board train, porter behind with bags. Lyrics from "Dixie." Postcard, circa 1934 (Box 25)
      Item #1132
    - A "Natural Finish" Card Made by Graycraft Card Co., Danville, VA Scene in tobacco curing barn. Men and boys sit around fireplace. Recto beneath image, "Boss Man Says: 'Keep Dat Fire Burnin'" Postcard, circa 1930 (Box 25)
      Item #1133
    - Asheville Postcard Co., Asheville, NC "D 66 Old-fashioned Southern Kitchen and Negro Mammy." Grotesque of black woman with pots before hearth. Postcard in color, circa 1930 (Box 25)
      Item #1134
    - Published by Herbert W. Pelton, Asheville, NC "No. 9 Building the Macadam Drives on the Blue Ridge Association Grounds, Black Mountain, NC" Men at work with sledge hammers. Postcard, circa 1915 (Box 25)
      Item #1135
    - T.P. & Co., New York, NY "A Colored Church." Two women on burro beside road near church. Postcard in color, circa 1930 (Box 25)
      Item #1136
    - Unknown printer "Clambake at Lookout Farm; Morgan House, Lookout Farm, Carl H. F. Kohl, Prop., Poughkeepsie, NY" Postcard, circa 1920 (Box 25)
      Item #1137
    - Unknown printer "Hampton Students. Hampton Institute, Va." Men in formation in dark uniforms, women in light dresses follow marching band. Postcard, circa 1914 (Box 25)
      Item #1138
    - Raphael Tuck, London "Armstrong-Slater Memorial Trade School, Hampton Institute, Va." Large institutional building behind stand of trees. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Stamped verso, "Postcard Series No. 2811, 'Hampton, Va.'"
      Item #1139
    - Raphael Tuck, London Virginia Hall, Hampton Institute, Hampton, VA. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Identified recto. Verso, "Postcard Series No. 2811. 'Hampton, Va.'"
      Item #1140
    - Raphael Tuck, London Academic Hall, Hampton Institute, Hampton, VA. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1141
    - Raphael Tuck, London Memorial Church, Hampton Institute, Hampton, VA. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Verso, "Postcard Series No. 2811, Hampton, Va.
      Item #1142
    - Raphael Tuck, London Huntington Memorial Library. Hampton Institute, Hampton, VA. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1143
    - Raphael Tuck, London The Farm Barn, Hampton Institute, Hampton, VA. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1144
    - Raphael Tuck, London Cleveland Hall, Hampton Institute, Hampton, VA. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1145
    - The Albertype Co., Brooklyn, NY Band, Hampton Institute in formation outdoors on school grounds. Postcard, circa 1933 (Box 25)
      Item #1146
    - Unknown printer School Battalion, Hampton Institute in formation on school grounds. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1147
    - The Albertype Co., Brooklyn, NY School Battalion. Hampton Institute in formation on school grounds. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Same view as 1147, different mount, sepia.
      Item #1148
    - The Albertype Co., Brooklyn, NY The Hampton Institute Choir. Postcard, circa 1925 (Box 25)
      Item #1149
    - The Albertype Co., Brooklyn, NY Band, Hampton Institute. Postcard, circa 1925 (Box 25, Folder 1028)
      Duplicates 1146.
      Item #1150
    - Unknown printer "Battalion of Cadets, The Hampton Normal and Agricultural Institute." Postcard, 1906 (Box 25)
      Item #1151
    - The Eagle Postcard View Co., New York NY Booker T. Washington writing at desk Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      In negative, "copy by Hyman." Stamped recto beneath image, "Dr. Booker T. Washington. Founder of Tuskegee Institute, ALA."
      Item #1152
    - M.T. Sheahan, Boston "M.T. Sheahan's Famous People 928." Small portrait of Booker T. Washington, long quote recto. Postcard, 1911 (Box 25)
      Item #1153
    - Unknown printer Booker T. Washington, Tuskegee Institute, Alabama. Postcard, circa 1950 (Box 25)
      Item #1154
    - Institute Book Shop, Tuskegee Institute, AL. Stamped recto beneath image, "Dr. George Washington Carver, Tuskegee Institute, Alabama." Postcard, circa 1960 (Box 25)
      Item #1155
    - A.P. Bedou, New Orleans, LA "Commencement Day Parade, Tuskegee Institute, Ala." Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1156
    - Unknown printer "Colored Women's Branch, Y.W.C.A., New York City." Postcard, 1924 (Box 25)
      Handwritten on image, "Reception Hall & Lobby, Y.W.C.A."
      Item #1157
    - The Hament-Romans Company, Baltimore, MD "Colored Victory Boys, Camp Merritt, N.J." Postcard, circa 1919 (Box 25)
      Duplicated 1159, 1160.
      Item #1158
    - The Hament-Romans Company, Baltimore, MD "Colored Victory Boys, Camp Merritt, N.J." Postcard, circa 1919 (Box 25)
      Duplicates 1158, 1160.
      Item #1159
    - The Hament-Romans Company, Baltimore, MD "Colored Victory Boys, Camp Merritt, N.J." Postcard, circa 1919 (Box 25)
      Duplicates 1158, 1159.
      Item #1160
    - Cole & Co., Asbury Park, NJ "Columbia Records: Note the Notes." Advertising card for Cole & Co., record dealers. Postcard, 1917 (Box 25)
      Item #1161
    - Unknown printer "1107 Darling Nelly Gray." Lyrics with sentimental image. Postcard in color, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1162
    - Jacobs & Co., Advertising, Clinton, SC "Colored Recruit...", copyright 1917. Postcard in color (Box 25)
      Item #1163
    - Franz Huld, Publisher, NY "No. 67, North and South United:" Black child cradled in embrace of white child. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1164
    - National Photograph Co., Chicago (copyright) "Compliments of Chas. H. Moore Oil Co., Cincinnati, Ohio" Advertising card. Black baby sitting crying, calendar for August, 1908 below. Postcard (Box 25)
      Item #1165
    - Unknown printer "The Musical Morrisons; Per. Address: Billboard." Formal single portraits: man in tuxedo on left; woman on right. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1166
    - The Albertype Co., Brooklyn, NY "Dr. E.C. Morris:" Oval of Dr. Morris on left; quote by him above flowers on right. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Recto, lower left, "Publ. by A.P. Bedou, N.O. LA."
      Item #1167
    - Unknown printer "Court Yard Kitchen, 820 St. Louis Street, New Orleans, La." Postcard, circa 1920 (Box 25, Folder 1029)
      Item #1168
    - Silvercraft-Made by the Dexter Press, Pearl River, NY "Tuskegee Students at O'Briens. 46953:" Waiters, busboys, cook stand in line in dining room. Postcard, circa 1945 (Box 25)
      Item #1169
    - Artvue Postcard Co., New York, NY "Church Rectory and Hall-St. Gabriel's Mission for Colored Passionist Fathers- Box 403, Greenville, N.C. Father Maurice C. P., Pastor." Postcard, circa 1925 (Box 25)
      Item #1170
    - W.W. Hixon & Co., Rockford, IL "House in which Gen'l Taylor was born, Louisville, Ky." Postcard in color, circa 1920 (Box 25)
      Item #1171
    - J.G. McCrorey & Co., New York, NY "Desolation, Memphis, Tenn." Apparent flood; families gathered on high ground surrounded by possessions. Postcard in color, circa 1908 (Box 25)
      Dated from postmark. Duplicates 1296.
      Item #1172
    - Raphael Tuck & Son, London "Series No. 2438" "St. Augustine, Fla.; Treasury Street the Narrowest Street in the U.S." Man stands at intersection of Bay and Treasury Streets. Postcard in color, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1173
    - Published expressly for F.W. Woolworth Co., Made in U.S.A. "A-28768" "Negro Baptizing in Mississippi River." Postcard in color, circa 1930 (Box 25)
      Item #1174
    - T.C. Co., Chicago, IL "88 The Old Oaken Bucket in Dixie Land:" Boys surround well; one drinks from bucket. Postcard in color, 1913 (Box 25)
      Posted from New York, 5 September, 1913.
      Item #1175
    - F.M. Kirby & Co., no location "Vegetable Vender, an every Morning scene on The Streets of Charleston, SC:" Man stands on sidewalk with load of vegetables on his head. Postcard in color, circa 1912 (Box 25)
      Item #1176
    - C.T. Photchrom, Chicago, IL "53 A Southern Basket Maker:" Man seated on crate making wicker baskets; dog nearby. Postcard in color, 1912 (Box 25)
      Item #1177
    - D. Goldberg, Newark, NJ U.S. Army and National Guard Series "Ginger Lime and Lemon, 5c! A Bulls-eye in Every Glass;" Troopers in field dress with rifles surround man in white jacket, straw hat, with two buckets. Postcard, circa 1905 (Box 25)
      Item #1178
    - Unknown printer "Williams' World-Famous Singers." Advertising card. Postcard in color, circa 1915 (Box 25)
      Item #1179
    - A "Colourpicture" Publication, Boston "James Montgomery Flagg. Jack Dempsey Knocks Out Jeff Willard, Toledo, O. July 4th, 1919 and Becomes Champion of the World." Postcard in color from painting, circa 1919 (Box 25)
      Stamped verso, "May I play host and say 'Hello' to you in my restaurant where food and friendliness are knockouts" signed by Dempsey
      Item #1180
    - Published by Thompson & Thompson, for "The World in Boston" "'The World in Boston Missionary Exposition' Negro Scene, American Missionary Association." Postcard, circa 1915 (Box 25)
      Duplicates 1123. See also 1234.
      Item #1181
    - Unknown printer "Souvenir Postcard, 49th B.M.C.G.U.O. of O.F. Atlantic City, N.J.;" at right image of "P.G.M. Peter Ogden;" at left building identified as "headquarter's Building, 12th & Spruce Streets, Phila." Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1182
    - Published by the Concessionaire, The Jamestown Amusement & Vending Co., Inc. Norfolk, VA "Negro Basket-Maker." Man seated in chair outside cabin making wicker baskets Postcard in color, 1907 (Box 25)
      Stamped verso, "1607--Jamestown Exposition--1907. Official Souvenir" See also 1177.
      Item #1183
    - The Rotograph Co., N.Y. City (Germany) "11824 Fresh Vegetables, Charleston, S.C." Young woman and young man both with vegetable baskets on their heads. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1184
    - Publ. by C.O. Tucker, Boston, MA No. 692, Made in Germany "Ben (Shine-um-up), Granville, Mass." Postcard. Faint legend in red within subject., circa 1920 (Box 25)
      Item #1185
    - Adolphe Selige Publ. Co., St. Louis "1789 Negro River Roustabouts." Two men sit on coiled rope on pallet. Postcard, 1905 (Box 25, Folder 1030)
      Item #1186
    - Pub. by the Acmegraph Co., Chicago, IL "5066 Serving Dinner on a Southern Plantation." Seated at long table behind large white house. Postcard in color, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1187
    - The Albertype Co., Brooklyn, NY "Is Glad I Came to Oklahoma." Boy stands in path holding large live turkey by the legs over his shoulder; cabin in background. Postcard, 1907 (Box 25)
      Lower left, recto, "copyright 1907 Geo B. Cornish, Arkansas City, Kans."
      Item #1188
    - Danforth & Co., Publishers, Homforth and New York (England) "Little Log Cabin:" old man seated before cabin head in hand; angels in halo at right; verse about death beneath image. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1189
    - Unknown printer "Jesus Died for Both." White man with beard, long hair holds white child on lap; black child kneels beside, lamb at his feet. Postcard, 1911 (Box 25)
      Printer's name illegible in half-tone recto.
      Item #1190
    - Unknown printer, Chicago "The Protesting Angel." Two children play at cliff's edge, "Little children fear not ...." Postcard, 1910 (Box 25)
      Copyright date, in subject.
      Item #1191
    - W.R. Thomson & Co., Richmond, VA "Re. C. No. 2 Interviewing Room, Army Reception Center, New Cumberland, Pa." Postcard, circa 1942 (Box 25)
      Item #1192
    - Hungerford Holbrook Co., Watertown, N.Y. "Camp of the 24th Infantry (Colored)." Postcard, 1908 (Box 25)
      In ink beneath image recto, "Pine Plains Jefferson Co NY Co. C. 2nd Regt."
      Item #1193
    - W. B. Garrison, Washington, D. C. "In Line for Mess, Colored Section, Camp Humphreys, Va." Postcard, circa 1917 (Box 25)
      Item #1194
    - Unknown printer "Cook's Quarters, Camp Bartlett, Westfield, Mass. Preparing the Soldiers' Feed'" Postcard (blue), circa 1918 (Box 25)
      Item #1195
    - Franz Huld, Publisher, NY "Cake Walk (Negro Dance) No. 1" Four performers in costume, mid dance. Postcard in color, 1898 (Box 25)
      "Private Mailing Card" verso. Of a set with 1197, 1198, 1199. Dated from Congressional authorization date.
      Item #1196
    - Franz Huld, Publisher, New York "Cake Walk (Negro Dance) No. 2" Four performers in costume, mid dance. Postcard in color, 1898 (Box 25)
      "Private Mailing Card" verso. Of a set with 1196, 1198, 1199. Dated from Congressional authorization date.
      Item #1197
    - Franz Huld, Publisher, NY "Cake Walk (Negro Dance) No. 3" Four performers in costume, mid dance. Postcard in color, 1898 (Box 25)
      "Private Mailing Card" verso. Of a set with 1196, 1197, 1199. Dated from Congressional authorization date.
      Item #1198
    - Franz Huld, Publisher, NY "Cake Walk (Negro Dance) No. 4" Four performers in costume, mid dance. Postcard in color, 1898 (Box 25)
      "Private Mailing Card" verso. Of a set with 1196, 1197, 1198. Dated from Congressional authorization date.
      Item #1199
    - Unknown printer "The Cake Walk on the Pier." Minstrel troupe performs outdoors; crowds all around. Postcard, circa 1905 (Box 25)
      Postmark date.
      Item #1200
    - The Hugh C. Leighton Co., Manufacturers, Portland, Me. U.S.A. 26378. Made in Germany. "A Negro Wedding Down South." Bride and groom face minister on wagon beneath arch, "Lincoln Heights." Very large crowd of witnesses. Postcard in color, 1908 (Box 25)
      Item #1201
    - H.H. Stratton, Chattanooga, TN "Sailors from Admiral Perry's Fleet Bathing at Honolulu, Hawaiian Islands, July, 1908." Postcard in color (Box 25)
      Item #1202
    - Hungerford-Holbrook Co., Publishers, Watertown, N.Y. "Camp of the 24th Infantry (Colored); Pine Camp, N.Y." Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25, Folder 1031)
      Duplicates 1193.
      Item #1203
    - "Genuine Curteich-Chicago 'C.T. Art- Colortone' Postcard" "Army Troops, Colored, Fort Leonard Wood, Missouri." Postcard in color, 1942 (Box 25)
      Dated by postmark.
      Item #1204
    - "Published Exclusively for Fort McClellan Exchange-Photo U.S. Army Signal Corps. Natural color Postcard made in U.S.A. by E. C. Kropp Co., Milwaukee, Wis.-(day)." "Colored Soldiers, Fort McClellan, Anniston, Ala.- 58." Troopers march past line of rucksacks beside train. Postcard in color, circa 1943 (Box 25)
      Item #1205
    - The Valentine & Sons' Publishing Co., Ltd., New York, Printed in Great Britain "Smoking Moose Meat." Men in forest smoking strips of meat over fire. Postcard in color, circa 1925 (Box 25)
      Item #1206
    - Detroit Publishing Company "13023 Stripping Tobacco." Men and women seated in large circle in warehouse processing tobacco. Postcard in color, circa 1925 (Box 25)
      Item #1207
    - "Genuine Curteich-Chicago 'C.T. Art- Colortone' Postcard" "Tobacco Ready for Curing in Tobacco- land." Tobacco leaves, looped and sticked being handed into curing barn. Postcard in color, circa 1950 (Box 25)
      Item #1208
    - Made in Germany. D. J. Hicks, Importer and Publisher, Beaumont, Texas "Logging Scene, near Beaumont, Tex." Teams of bullocks harnessed to wagons with logs. Postcard in color, 1905 (Box 25)
      Item #1209
    - Western Publishing & Novelty Co., Los Angeles, CA "852-Home of Eddie 'Rochester' Anderson, Los Angeles, California" "NBC Comedian and Screen Star" "1B H1018." Image of home with small bust of actor above left. Postcard in color, circa 1943 (Box 25)
      Dated by postmark in duplicate.
      Item #1210
    - Western Publishing & Novelty Co., Los Angeles, CA "852-Home of Eddie 'Rochester' Anderson Los Angeles, California, NBC Comedian and Screen Star 1B H1018." Image of home with small bust of actor above left. Postcard in color, circa 1943 (Box 25)
      Duplicates 1210. Dated by postmark.
      Item #1211
    - H.L. Woeller, Buffalo, NY Dresden, Germany "U.S. Mail Carrier, Lake Helen, Fla." Man stands beside buckboard before house. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1212
    - Published by Florida Souvenir Co., St. Augustine, Fla.-Natural Color Postcard Made In U.S.A. by E. C. Kropp Co., Milwaukee, Wis.-(JEL) "Oldest House in the United States, St. Augustine, Florida-SK." Antique Spanish house; driver with horse and carriage sits out front. Postcard in color, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1213
    - Published by Southern Bargain House, Richmond, VA "Lakeside Park, Richmond, Va." Man feeds swans from boat at boathouse. Building on rise in background. Postcard in color, circa 1912 (Box 25)
      Item #1214
    - Unknown printer "Dinah's Shack at Palo Alto, California ½ Spring Chicken on Toast-50c." Cars parked beside restaurant under trees; wait-staff out front and at window. Postcard, circa 1929 (Box 25)
      Item #1215
    - Unknown printer "Bennett College, Greensboro, N.C." Photographs of Girls' Dormitory, Boys' Dormitory, and Kent Home. Postcard, 1907 (Box 25)
      Item #1216
    - Souvenir Postcard Co., New York "15284-A and M College for the Colored Race, Greensboro, N.C." Postcard (green). Postmark date, circa 1908 (Box 25)
      Item #1217
    - Unknown printer "St. Joseph's Mission Church and School for Colored, New Bern, North Carolina..." Postcard, circa 1920 (Box 25)
      Item #1218
    - Silvercraft-Made by Dexter Press, Pearl River, NY. Published by Stewart's Photo Studio, Akron, Ohio. "5655 Commemorating the 45th Anniversary of Rev. R.A. Jones, Pastor of Second Baptist Church of Akron, Ohio." View of church with full face oval of pastor superimposed above. Postcard, circa 1915 (Box 25)
      Item #1219
    - The Rotograph Co., N.Y. City (Germany) "10359 Plucking Feathers from male Ostrich. The Florida Ostrich Farm, Jacksonville." Two men with ostrich in "Plucking Pen." Postcard, circa 1905 (Box 25)
      Dated from copyright stamp.
      Item #1220
    - Martin Postcard Co., no location "Carving One of Our Watermelons." Distorted perspectives: huge watermelons being cut and eaten. Postcard, 1909 (Box 25)
      Item #1221
    - Pub. by the Atkinson News Co, Tilton, NH for Howe's Shop, Southern Pines, NC "Dewberry Field, Sandhill Section of North Carolina." Berry pickers with baskets in berry field. Postcard, circa 1920 (Box 25)
      Item #1222
    - National Art Views Co., New York, NY "No. 744 Scene in a Sugar Plantation." Horse and bullock drawn wagons and plows; men afoot and on horseback; grass roofed barns. Postcard, circa 1915 (Box 25, Folder 1032)
      Item #1223
    - The Rotograph Co., New York, NY (Germany) "743 Lunch at a Sugar Plantation." Workers eating before grass hut. Postcard, circa 1915 (Box 25)
      Item #1224
    - Franz Huld, Publisher, New York, NY "No. 717 Celery Farm 'in boards', Sanford, Fla." Postcard, circa 1915 (Box 25)
      Item #1225
    - Unknown printer "John Bunny 'Bunny in Funnyland'" Man seated backwards on chair holds walking stick. Postcard, circa 1922 (Box 25)
      Item #1226
    - Copyright 1900 by C.L. Legerton; H.A. Rost Prt. & Pub Co., New York, NY "News Boy:" Barefoot boy, papers under his arm, cap. Postcard (Box 25)
      "Private Mailing Card" stamped verso
      Item #1227
    - The Albertype Co., Brooklyn, NY Man in overalls stands on links, golf clubs right shoulder. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1228
    - Unknown printer "A Ninety-Year-Old Cotton Picker." Old woman picks cotton. Postcard, 1912 (Box 25)
      Item #1229
    - A. Selige Souvenir Postcard Co., St. Louis "West Point Mississippi; Down where the Cotton Blossoms Grow." Postcard, circa 1904 (Box 25)
      Item #1230
    - Selige Pub. St. Louis "145 From the Cotton Fields, Clay Co., Miss." Eight mule team harnessed to wagon with bales of cotton; driver up. Postcard, circa 1905 (Box 25)
      Item #1231
    - Unknown printer Craddock Terry Co.'s exhibit of "The Old Virginia shoe shop" at the Jamestown Exhibition: Alfred Leigh, former slave, making and repairing shoes. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1232
    - Published by the Jefferson Hotel, Pine Bluff, Ark.; Made in Germany "Cotton Scene, Pine St., Pine Bluff, Ark." Street lined with bales of cotton scale in background. Postcard, circa 1908 (Box 25)
      Item #1233
    - Published by Thompson & Thompson "For the World in Boston". "The World in Boston Missionary Exposition; Negro Scene, American Missionary Association"; black people standing before sets of log cabins; man in chains by bow of ship. Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Set with 1123, 1181.
      Item #1234
    - The Dexter Press, Pearl River, NY "Bedford Inn-Colored Tourist Home, 203 Monroe St., ... Fayetteville, N. C." Postcard, circa 1920 (Box 25)
      Item #1235
    - The Albertype Co., Brooklyn, NY "Slave Cabins at the Hermitage, Savannah, Ga." Postcard, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1236
    - ZIM, no location "13007B3 Station of the Underground Railroad, Ripley, Ohio;" House stands atop slight rise. Postcard in color, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Same house as 1239; different view.
      Item #1237
    - C.D. Hurd, Publisher, Books & Stationery, Made in Germany. "The Old Stone House, Clinton, Iowa. This house was a place of refuge for fugitive slaves during slavery days." Postcard in color, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1238
    - Tom Jones Pub. Cincinnati, OH "Grand Central Station of Underground R.R. 1850" "Greetings from Ripley, O." Postcard, circa 1906 (Box 25)
      Same house as 1237; different view. Dated from postmark.
      Item #1239
    - Gt. The Metropolitan News & Pub. Co., Boston, Mass. & Germany, Printed in Germany "The Magee House (built 1797) used as an Underground Slave Station, during Slavery Days." Postcard in light color, 1920 (Box 25)
      Item #1240
    - The Meriden Gravure Company, Meriden, CT "The Frissell Community House, Penn School. St. Helena Island, S.C." Building stands among trees; students out front. Postcard, circa 1925 (Box 25)
      Item #1241
    - Genuine Curteich-Chicago "C.T. Photo -Varicolor" Postcard "Domestic Science Building-Piney Woods School-Piney Woods, Mississippi. D-7662." Postcard in light color, circa 1925 (Box 25)
      Item #1242
    - Jacobs & Company, Clinton, SC "Bell Street School (Colored), Clinton, S.C." Postcard, circa 1930 (Box 25)
      Item #1243
    - J. H. Conner Drug Co., New Albany, IN "School for Colored People, New Albany, Ind." Postcard in color, circa 1910 (Box 25)
      Item #1244
    - Published by Powers Curiosity Store, Macon, GA "Prominent Colored Churches, Macon, Ga." Portraits of First Baptist, Stewart A.M. Episcopal, and Tremont- Temple Baptist Churches. Postcard in color (Box 25)
      Item #1245
    - Peter P. Jones, Chicago, IL; Published by Wm. Foster Music Co., Chicago "Institutional Church (Colored) Dearborn St., Near 39th St., Chicago." Postcard in color, 1912 (Box 25)
      Item #1246